Sasuke's Chakra...
《香燐 : サスケのチャクラが…》
変化した…。
...changed!
(重吾)
ゲハハハ… また オレのコピー野郎か!?
Not another copy of me!
ハッハッハッハ！
《サスケ…》
Sasuke...
しかし 部分変化ができるとは
たいした野郎だぜ！
But you're quite a guy to be able to do
a Partial Transformation!
呪印を扱うのが うめえな！
You're good at controlling
your Curse Mark!
コイツは強え！
君麻呂以来のコピー野郎だぜ！
He's strong! Haven't seen a copycat
this good since Kimimaro.
(サスケ)争う気はない。
I have no intention of fighting.
お前に話があるだけだ。 重吾。
I only wish to talk to you, Jugo.
話？
Talk...?!
お前を ここから出してやる。
I'm getting you out of here.
Get me out of here?!
ここから 出してやるだと！
フフフ… アハハハ！
バカじゃねえのか！
アイツがいねえんじゃ…。
Are you crazy?! Without him...
アイツがいねえんじゃ…➡
Without him...
オレは ここからは
出られねえんだよ！
I can't...leave this place.
((うわっ… やめろ！
Stop!
ぐわあっ！
やめてくれ！ うわ～っ！
Please stop!
うわ～っ！
やぁ お前たち…
元気にしていたかい？
Oh...guys... How have you been?
ワン ワン！
坊主 どこに行くつもりだい？
Kid, where are you going?
命が惜しければ
この先には行かんほうがいい。
If you value your life,
don't go beyond this point.
鬼が棲んどるからのぉ…。
A demon lives there.
(君麻呂)鬼？
A demon?
He's known as "Bipolar Jugo."
ソイツは 天秤の重吾と呼ばれとる。
あれを見んさい。 重吾のせいで➡
Look at that.
Because of Jugo,
no one lives in that village, to this day.
あの村は今や 住む者もおらん。
あやつに近づいて
生きて帰った者はいない。
No one's ever gotten close to him
and come back alive.
悪いことは言わん。
引き返すことだ。
I don't mean to lecture you.
But you should go back.
ワンワンワン。
What? You've followed me?
なんだ ついてきちゃったのか？
でも ここからはダメだよ。
絶対に来るんじゃない。
But stop where you are.
You must not come.
さぁ お前は お前のウチにお帰り。
Now, go back to your own home.
(重吾)来るな… 来るなよ！
Don't come near me! Go away!
If you come here, I'll kill you!
来たら殺す！
この中に来たヤツは殺す!!
I'll kill anyone who comes in here!
ワン ワンワン。
誰？ 来ないで。
Who is it?
Go away!
来るな！
来るなって言ってるだろ!!
Go away! I said to go away!
(殺すぞ))
I'll kill you...
《君麻呂…》
Kimimaro...
Formation!
I'll say it once more.
I have no intention of fighting.
もう一度言う。 争う気はない。
お前を連れ出しにきただけだ。
オレとともに来い。
I came to get you out of here.
Come with me.
オレはもう ここから
出られないんだよ！
I can't leave here anymore!
うおぉ～!!
Sasuke!
サスケ！
Just kill that guy...Sasuke!
やっちゃえ そんなヤツ。 サスケ！
逃がすか！
As if I'll let you get away!
(水月)ったく 何だよ ここは！
Geez! What is this place?!
あっ… ひどいな。
キミだろ？ ボクを騙したのは。
You're mean!
You tricked me, didn't you?
アンタが勝手に
迷子になったんだろうが。
You went and got lost on your own.
I just followed your directions!
ボクは キミの言ったほうに
歩いてっただけだろう。
ウチが騙したっていうのか!?
Are you accusing me of tricking you?!
アンタを騙して
ウチに何の得があるっていうんだ？
How would I benefit from
tricking you anyway?
サスケと２人っきりになれるだろ。
You can be alone with Sasuke.
A-As if I'd want such a thing...!
だっ… 誰が そんなこと
考えるって思って…。
えっと… その… フン！
Umm... I mean...
まあいいや。 それより➡
Well, whatever.
But what's going on here?
いったい これは
どういうことなんだよ？
重吾が暴れたんだ。
Jugo went wild...
So the two of you went to Jugo,
after all.
やっぱり…
２人だけで重吾の所に来たのか。
サスケは？
重吾と外に出てった。
Where's Sasuke?
He went out with Jugo.
まぁ サスケのことだから
簡単にはやられないと思うけど。
Well, it's Sasuke.
He won't get beaten that easily.
さぁ どうかな…。
I wonder...
重吾 強くなってるのか。
まあね。
So Jugo has gotten strong...?
You could say that...
そういえば アイツは自分から➡
By the way, you said that he willingly
came to Orochimaru, right?
大蛇丸のところに来た
と言ってたな。
あぁ。
Yeah...
なんで？
Why?
To reform himself.
更正するためだろ。
更正？
Reform himself...?
きっと 重吾にとっては
大蛇丸のアジトは➡
It's possible that...for Jugo,
Orochimaru's hideout was like
a sanctuary.
更正施設のような
ものだったんだろう。
What does Jugo wish to be
reformed from?
重吾が何を更正したい？
It's like an addiction...
いわゆる中毒と同じだ。
自分だけではどうにもできない。
He can't do anything about it
on his own.
Huh?
殺人衝動を抑えたかったのさ。
He wanted to suppress his urge to kill.
ハハハハ！ 殺す!!
Kill!
うぉ～！
お前は わかっていない！
You don't understand...!
オレはもう
ここから逃げられないんだ！
I can no longer escape from this place!
((お前も殺してやる!!
I'll kill you too!
うぉ～！
(君麻呂)なるほど…
すさまじい力だ。
I see... Your strength is amazing...
I thought I was a goner.
(君麻呂)ボクもやられるかと思った。
(重吾)だ… 誰だ お前！
Wh-Who are you...?
君麻呂…。 ボクはキミを捜しに来た。
Kimimaro... I came in search of you.
キミも
大蛇丸様のところに来ないか？
Would you...
like to go to Lord Orochimaru too?
大蛇丸？
Orochimaru...?
大蛇丸様のところには➡
There are many people with
Lord Orochimaru
キミやボクのようなヤツがたくさんいる。
孤独なんだろう？
that are just like you and I...
You're all alone, aren't you?
大蛇丸様のところに来れば
キミはもう孤独じゃなくなる。
If you go to Lord Orochimaru,
you won't be alone anymore.
I'm not normal.
I can't control myself.
オレは まともじゃないんだ！
オレは自分が抑えられない。
いつ
仲間を殺しだすかもわからない！
There's no telling when I'll start killing
the people around me.
I won't get killed.
ボクは やられない。
ボクは そんなに弱くない。
I'm not that weak.
お前 オレが怖くないのか？
Aren't you...afraid of me?
怖くない。 重吾。
No, I'm not, Jugo.
ボクが キミのオリになってあげる。
I will become your cage...
(ボクが そばにいるかぎり
キミの魂は自由だ))
As long as I'm by your side...
your spirit will be free.
ヘヘヘヘ！ 今 ぶっ殺してやる！
I'll beat you to death!
((えっ それは本当なのか？
Huh? Is that...true?
あぁ。 キミの体から
取り出した酵素をボクの中に入れる。
Yes. I'm going to absorb the enzyme
from your body into my own.
ボクもキミと同じように
呪印の力を得るわけだ。
Just like you,
I will possess the power of the Curse Mark.
待てよ… 呪印は
誰にでも適合するわけじゃない。
Hold on a minute.
The Curse Mark doesn't adapt
to just anyone.
もし適合しなかったら…。
If it doesn't adapt...
知っている。 その時は ボクは死ぬ。
I know... At that moment, I'll die.
それなら そんなことはやめろ！
治療の一環なんだ。
If you know, then stop this!
It's part of the treatment.
ボクの身は 病に
むしばまれつつある。
My body is being eaten away
by disease.
キミの呪印は その進行を
遅らせてくれるかもしれない。
Perhaps your Curse Mark
will slow its progress.
キミの力が
ボクを救ってくれるわけだ。
Your power will save me.
そんなに心配するな。
大丈夫 ボクたちは親友だ。
Don't worry so much.
It's all right. We're best friends.
(キミの力が
ボクを拒絶するわけがない))
There is no way your power
will reject me.
《君麻呂… どうしてお前は➡
Kimimaro...why did you...
お前は オレを置いていったんだ！》
Why did you...leave me and die!
う～お～っ!!
なんだ!?
What?!
前とは違う能力を
使っているね 重吾。
You're using a different technique
than before, Jugo. It's solid.
かたいし。
やめろ 水月。
Stop it, Suigetsu.
そうか テメエは水月。 思い出したぜ。
That's right!
You're Suigetsu. I remember now.
やっぱり コイツは やばいよ サスケ。
This guy is dangerous,
after all, Sasuke.
サスケ？
Sasuke...?
争いに来たんじゃない。
オレが話す。
We didn't come here to fight.
Let me talk to him.
話して 言葉が
通じるようなヤツじゃないよ。
I doubt that anything
you say will get through to him.
力ずくで 連れてくまで！
You just have to take him by force!
は～っ！
２人とも やめろ！
Stop it, both of you!
Keep going! Just kill each other off!
《いいぞ！ 共倒れしちまえ！》
は～っ！
おら～!!
お前ら オレに殺されたいのか？
Do you both...want me to kill you?
《今の…
本気の殺意だったじゃないか…》
Just now...that was real bloodthirst.
《た… たまんない サスケ…》
Y-You're irresistible...Sasuke...
あぁ… あぁ…。
あっ あ ああ…。
は 早く鍵をかけてよ～！
H-Hurry up and lock me in!
重吾 オレは
お前を連れ出しに来ただけだ。
Jugo... I only came to free you.
オレとともに来い。
Come with me.
ビビりすぎでしょう。
違う。 そうじゃねえよ。
He's too scared.
No... That's not it.
オレはもう
人を殺したくないんだよ。
I don't want to kill anymore people.
外になんか出たくないんだ。
放っといてくれよ！
I don't want to go outside...
Leave me alone!
なに？ あれ。
すごい二重人格だね。
What is this?
Talk about split personality...
言ったろ。 重吾は 自分でも➡
I told you so...
Jugo has this uncontrollable urge to kill.
どうにもならない
殺人衝動に駆られるって。
自分を コントロールできないでいる。
He's unable to suppress the urge
ホントは
殺人なんてしたくないのさ。
even though he really doesn't want
to kill people.
オレは また いつ
人を殺したくなるかわからない。
I don't know when
I'll kill someone again.
いいから 鍵をかけてくれよ～！
So just put the lock on!
やっぱり 重吾はやばいよ サスケ。
See, this guy is dangerous, Sasuke.
ヤツの目の前じゃ 歩くことすら
落ち着いてできやしない。
I can't even walk in front of him
without getting nervous.
お前ら いったいなんなんだよ…。
オレに かまうなよ！
What's with you guys?!
Just leave me alone!
大蛇丸は 死んだ。
Orochimaru is dead.
このアジトも 崩壊した。
And this hideout has been destroyed.
ここにいたら お前も終わりだ。
If you stay here, you'll die as well.
それでいい。
これ以上 人を殺したくはない。
That's fine with me...
I don't want to kill anyone ever again!
安心しろ。 オレが
お前のオリになってやる。
Don't worry...
I will become your cage.
オレが お前を止めてやる。
I will stop you.
(重吾)お前に何ができる。
What can you do?
オレの衝動を止められるのは
君麻呂だけだ。
The only one who can make
these urges stop is Kimimaro.
君麻呂がいないなら
外へは出ない！
Without Kimimaro, I won't leave!
君麻呂って
たしか かぐや一族の…。
Kimimaro? You mean
of the Kaguya clan...?
あぁ 重吾と君麻呂は
特に 大蛇丸のお気に入りで➡
Yeah... Jugo and Kimimaro were
especially favored by Orochimaru.
実験体として このアジトで
ずっと一緒にされていたからな。
They were kept together in this hideout
for human experiments
for a long time.
それに 君麻呂は 強かった。
Plus, Kimimaro was strong...
貴重な実験体である
重吾の暴走を➡
Jugo was valuable for
human experiments
傷つけずに 止めることが
できたのは➡
and Kimimaro was the only one able to
stop Jugo's rampages without hurting him.
ヤツだけだったって話だ。
でも その男って たしかもう…。
But I thought that guy was already...
あぁ。
重吾
君麻呂は オレのために死んだ➡
Yeah...
Jugo... Kimimaro died for my sake.
もういない。
He's no longer here.
(重吾)お前のために死んだ？
じゃあ お前が…➡
Died for your sake?!
Then you're...
うちは… サスケか？
Sasuke Uchiha...?
そうだ。
Yes.
うちは… サスケ。
Sasuke...
Uchiha...
((どうして 病人のお前が
駆り出される!?
Why are you being sent out?
You're sick!
今まで こんなことは。
This has never happened before...
うちはサスケ…➡
Sasuke Uchiha...
ボクの代わりに 大蛇丸様の
器となる男。
The man who is taking my place
as Lord Orochimaru's vessel...
彼を連れ帰るのが目的だ。
It's to bring him in.
そこまでする
価値のある男なのか？
Is he worth going that far?
器になるべき存在は➡
If you take me out of the running
as a vessel,
ボクを除けば 彼をおいて
他にはいない。
then there is no one else.
彼は ボクの生まれ変わりのような
存在だ。
He is like my reincarnation.
ボクは命を懸けて 彼を連れ帰る。
I will risk my life to bring him here.
キミには 感謝しているよ 重吾。
I'm grateful to you, Jugo.
キミの力が
ボクを さらに強くしてくれた。
Your power made me much stronger.
(それじゃあ 重吾 また来るよ))
Well Jugo... I'll be back again.
《そういうことか… 君麻呂》
Is that how it is...Kimimaro.
これで オレが考えていたメンバーは
揃った。
Now...
I have all the members I had in mind.
これから オレの目的を言う。
So I will tell you my goal.
オレの目的は 暁の うちはイタチを
殺すことだ。
My goal is to kill Itachi Uchiha
of the Akatsuki.
やっぱりね。
Thought so...
《うちはイタチって…
実の兄じゃん！》
Itachi Uchiha...?
But that's his brother!
そこで お前たちの力を借りたい。
And I want to borrow your strength for that.
もちろん 強制はしない。
Naturally, I won't force you.
香燐 お前は用があるって
言っていたな。
Karin... You said you had business
to take care of.
どうする？
そ そうだな。
What will you do?
W-Well... On second thought,
it's not that urgent...
よく考えたら 別に
あまり 急ぐ用でも…。
Karin... Be honest with yourself.
香燐 キミは素直になったら
どうなんだ？
ホントは サスケとずっと一緒に
いたいだけなんじゃないのか？
Isn't being with Sasuke
all you really want?
そ そんなわけあるか！
Th-That's not true!
Whoever said such a thing?
誰がそんなこと
あるのか 言ったこと。
それ えっと。
ほ～ら 図星だ。
That's...! I...!!
See, I hit it right on the mark.
だから ろれつが回らなくなる。
バレバレ。
That's why you're speechless.
So obvious.
ホントは知ってんだよ。
昔 キミはサスケに…。
I know all about it...
Long ago...
you had a crush on Sasuke...
水月 香燐をあおるのはよせ。
Suigetsu, don't get Karin so worked up...
協力はしろと言ったはずだ。
I thought I told you to be cooperative.
わかったよ。 悪かったね 香燐。
All right... Sorry, Karin.
けどね 悪いけど ボクは
サスケにべったりくっついていくよ。
But as much as you hate it...
I'm sticking to Sasuke like glue.
霧隠れ七刀のうちのひと振り➡
At least until I possess one
of the Seven Hidden Mist Blades...
うちはイタチと組んでる
干柿鬼鮫の大刀 鮫肌を➡
Kisame Hoshigaki's
Great Shark Fin sword.
この手にするまではね。
ただの刀集めかよ。 くだらねえ。
So you're just sword collecting?
How lame...
水月。
わかってるよ。
Suigetsu...
I know. Jugo, what about you?
重吾 キミはどうする？
君麻呂は サスケを
自分の生まれ変わりだと言って➡
Kimimaro used to say that
you were his reincarnation, Sasuke...
命を懸けて守った。
And he bet his life to protect you.
だから オレも お前が
どれほどの忍びか見届けてやる。
So I want to see with my own eyes
just how great of a Ninja you are.
決まりだな。
Then it's all set!
どういうことだってばよ。
もう大蛇丸はいねえのに➡
What's the matter with him?
Orochimaru is dead,
so why isn't he returning to the village?
なんでアイツは
里に戻ってこねえんだ？
(自来也)サスケのヤツは
復讐に取り憑かれとる。
Sasuke is possessed by
the desire for revenge.
兄であるうちはイタチを殺すために
暁に近づく気だのぉ。
He intends to approach the Akatsuki
in order to kill his older brother Itachi.
あの野郎 まだ…。 クソッ。
That guy!
Is he still...? Dammit!
今後 オレたちは４人で動く。
From this point on, we move together.
そしてこれより
我ら小隊は 蛇と名乗る。
And henceforth,
we will call ourselves... Hebi.
じゃあ オレたちも
さっさと行くってばよ。
Well, let's get going.
まだ 暁狩りの任務は
継続中なんだろ？
Operation "Track Akatsuki"
is still ongoing, right?
(綱手)ああ。
なら サスケに会うために➡
Yes...
If we hunt down that
Akatsuki member first
最も確率の高い暁のメンバー
ソイツを捜すってばよ。
we'll definitely run into
Sasuke eventually!
蛇の目的は ただ一つ。
Hebi has but one objective...
つまり オレたちが狙うのは…。
In other words, our target is...
うちは…。
イタチだ。
Itachi...
Uchiha!
I'll tell you a story from
when I was still just a kid.
It was during the final days of
the Third Great Ninja War.
Due to the long war with other nations,
the Leaf was suffering from
an unprecedented lack of war capability.
It was during such time
when that incident occurred.
It was my first mission as a Jonin.
Next time: "Kakashi Chronicles~
A Boy's Life on the Battlefield ~ Part 1"
Lady Katsuyu, may I ask you a question?
Yes?
How did you get here?
Oh, that was...
So, please join Sakura
as soon as possible.
As soon as possible...
Everyone is waiting for you!
Understood.
However, I can't walk that fast...
Oh no!!
This is nothing, they're all waiting...
(エバーグリーン)ナツ…
どうして ここに？
Ah, the sunlight... the dryness...
(エルフマン)びっくりさせやがって…。
Oh no! It's a slug monster!
Get me some salt, salt!
(ゼレフ)ナツ…。
Please wait, I'm not...
You went through all
that trouble for us...?!
Oh no, my effort was nothing
compared to yours.
Not at all!
We didn't know any of that...
Here, Naruto. Come here and
apologize to her with me!
Whoa, for what?